oddup.com 2016-04-29

# Oddup

## **PRIVACY POLICY**

####  Oddup seeks to improve consumer’s online experience, and building and maintaining your trust is an important part of mission. We understand that our success in achieving this goal will be partially based on how we protect your privacy and safeguard your personal information. This Privacy Policy will explain how we will achieve this goal while providing you with an optimal online consumer experience. 

####  The first thing you need to know is that this Privacy Policy applies to personal information (as defined by applicable law) collected, processed, and used by oddup.com, the upcoming Oddup mobile application, our platform, platform technology, and any other of your websites, apps, developer platforms, and other products and services that we presently offer or will offer in the future (“Oddup Services”). By using Oddup Services you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to those of the Oddup community who register accounts with us and those of you who do not but visit our site or otherwise make use of Oddup Services. We ask, therefore, that you take the time to read this Privacy Policy carefully before registering an account with us or using Oddup Services. 

### **ODDUP**

####  Oddup is a Hong Kong registered company. Our full name is **Oddup Limited** and we have a registered address of **1102, Hing Tai Commercial Building, 114 Wing Lok Street, Sheung Wan, Hong Kong.** Your personal information that we collect, process, and use in providing you with Oddup Services will be controlled by this company. Your data is stored in our private database. We presently do not have any subsidiaries, branch offices, or related or affiliated entities nor are we part of a larger corporate group. We do one day hope that this changes. If that is the case then we will ensure that such an entity or entities will be bound by this Privacy Policy and will notify you of any change of the data controller or where the data is stored should that occur. 

### **I. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

####  We collect personal information provided directly by you as well as personal information and other information about your use of the Oddup Services. You consent to said collection by submitting personal information and information to us and through your use of the Oddup Services subject to this Privacy Policy and User Agreement. The majority of personal information and information collected is necessary to provide you with the Oddup Services and for the processing and use under III of this Privacy Policy. Where the collection of personal information is not strictly necessary then it is being provided to us voluntarily. 

##### **REGISTERING**

####  When you get started and register an account with Oddup, we collect information from you that includes your name, e-mail address, password, language preference, time of sign in and out, and ADD OTHERS. (“Account Information”) We will also collect your IP address, MAC address, geographic location, log files, browser, information about your device, and ADD OTHERS. (“Data Log”) 

##### **PERSONALIZING**

####  Once you have established an account with Oddup, you will have the option to personalize that account by adding additional personal information. This includes adding a photo, your geographic location, your gender, preferences, and other information voluntarily provided by you to improve your profile and your use of Oddup Services. (“Profile Information”)You understand that this information will appear within the Oddup community and will be public. You are always free to remove the additional personal information or adjust your privacy settings. 

##### **VOUCHING**

####  Once you begin to use Oddup Services, we will collect information automatically from you on an ongoing basis as part of us providing those services to you. This information includes, in part, your Account Information, Profile Information, and Data Log. We will also collect information on how you use Oddup Services and collect information related to your participation in the Oddup community including that information and content provided by yourself. 

##### **JUST VISITING**

####  If you visit our site or make use of our services without signing into your account or without an account then a Data Log and related information will be collected on your visit or use. 

##### **THIRD-PARTY SERVICES**

####  We will receive information when you use your Oddup account to access a third-party site, service, or application in relation to Oddup Services. We may also receive information when you use a third-party account, site, service, or application with your Oddup account for Oddup Services. You are free not to make use of these features. 

##### **SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION**

####  We do not ask users to submit information that could be sensitive personal information under applicable law. If you choose to submit sensitive personal information through your use of the Oddup Services, you acknowledge that the submission is voluntary and consensual, as would be any subsequent processing and use as a result of the collection. 

##### **LEGAL**

####  We collect personal information as and if required or permitted by law. 

##### **CONSENT**

####  We collect additional personal information where we have obtained your consent. 

### **II. WHAT ABOUT COOKIES AND WHAT IS YOUR COOKIE POLICY?**

####  Yes. We use cookies and similar technology to allow us to optimize your use of the Oddup Services. If you are unfamiliar with cookies then let’s take a minute to explain cookies and our cookie policy. 

##### **COOKIES**

####  Cookies are small text files or pieces of information that are stored on the browser of your computer or other device. Cookies make it easier for us to provide the Oddup Services by allowing us to identify your device and also by allowing you to remain logged in. Cookies also allow us to better understand how you use Oddup Services and allow us to better tailor our services to your interests and needs. Some cookies may contain personal information or could become personal information when other information is incorporated. 

##### **TYPES**

####  We use two types of cookies: session and persistent. Session cookies are created temporarily in your browser's subfolder while you are visiting a website. Session cookies will be deleted once you leave a site. Persistent cookie files remain valid in your browser's subfolder unless manually deleted by you or until the cookie’s expiry date. 

##### **HOW WE USE COOKIES**

####  The cookies that we use fall into the following categories: 

##### **STRICTLY NECESSARY COOKIES**

####  These types of cookies enable you to use our site and its features. Disabling these cookies can affect how our site performs and may prevent you from making use of all of its services and features. 

##### **FUNCTIONALITY COOKIES**

####  These cookies are used to remember settings when you return to our site so as to improve your visit as well as to allow us to provide services to you. 

##### **ANALYTICAL AND PERFORMANCE COOKIES**

####  These cookies help us to analyze and understand how  you interact and use our site and also on other sites where the Oddup community may post content. 

##### **AD COOKIES**

####  These cookies keep a record of your online activities and the links and advertisements you have clicked. These allow us to deliver content and advertisements that are more relevant to the your interests and may be used to provide specific advertising or to limit advertisements seen by you. 

##### **SECURITY COOKIES**

####  These cookies support additional security features on the site. 

##### **THIRD-PARTY**

####  We also allow the use of Third-Party cookies by service providers and our business partners. These cookies are not placed by Oddup and we do not have control over, management of, or access to them. These cookies collect information about your visit to our site for that third-party but the cookies should not collect or contain personal information. 

##### **YOUR OPTIONS**

####  If you do not want to receive cookies then you are free to adjust the settings in your browser. We cannot guarantee though that the site and all of its services will operate properly or can we guarantee that you will be provided with the optimal Oddup experience. 

### **III. HOW DO WE PROCESS AND USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND INFORMATION?**

####  We process and use your personal information to operate Oddup as well as for the express purposes set out below. You consent to said processing and use by submitting personal information and information to us and through your use of the Oddup Services subject to this Privacy Policy and User Agreement. The majority of personal information and information processed and used is necessary to provide you with the Oddup Services. Where the processing and use of personal information is not strictly necessary then it is being provided to us voluntarily and with consent for purposes set out below. 

##### **SERVICES**

####  We process and use your personal information to allow you to participate in the Oddup community and to provide you with the Oddup Services as well as to allow us to improve the provision of those services to you. 

##### **CUSTOMIZATION**

####  We process and use your personal information to allow for your Oddup experience to be optimal by, at times, customizing information, content, and communications being provided to you. 

##### **COMMUNICATIONS**

####  We process and use your personal information to allow you to communicate with other Oddup users. You understand that your online communications with other users will be stored as part of providing the Oddup Services to you. We will also process and use your personal information to communicate with you. Oddup communications will include communications related to your account and our services, administrative communications related to your account, and promotional and marketing communications. You may opt out of promotional or marketing communications at any time. 

##### **THIRD-PARTY SERVICES**

####  We process and use your personal information to allow you to use third-party services, accounts, and platforms as part of the Oddup Services as well as to allow you to use your Oddup account on third-party services, accounts, and platforms. 

##### **ADMINISTRATIVE AND SERVICES PROVIDERS**

####  We process and use your personal information for administrative purposes related to maintaining, operating, and improving the Oddup Services and community. This includes processing and use by affiliated or related entities as well as service providers hired by Oddup to provide services related to providing you with the Oddup Services to provide services to Oddup. 

##### **MARKETING AND PROMOTION**

####  We process and use your personal information to identify and share marketing and promotional information on products and services from Oddup or delivered by Oddup on behalf of a third-party partner. You may opt out of promotional or marketing communications at any time. We may also process and use your public content on our site or on third-party sites but with attribution to your account or name. 

##### **RESEARCH AND ANALYSIS**

####  We process and use your personal information to carry out research and analysis to improve Oddup Services and the Oddup community. This research and analysis may be information of individual or aggregate in nature. 

##### **BUSINESS PURPOSES**

####  We may process and use information collected by Oddup as part of providing the Oddup Services that is no longer personal information, for example it has been anonymized and aggregated or is not considered personal information under applicable law, for our own commercial purposes.  

##### **CHANGE OF CONTROL OR SALE**

####  We may process and use your personal information to facilitate a change of control or sale of Oddup or to facilitate a restructuring or other corporate rearrangement. 

##### **LEGAL**

####  We may process and use your personal information as required or permitted by law. 

##### **CONSENT**

####  We may process and use your personal information outside of the original purpose for which it was collected where we have obtained your fresh consent. 

### **IV. WHO HAS ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION?**

##### **US**

####  Your personal information will be under the control of Oddup. It will be available to us as well as to any affiliated companies or to any companies, entities, or individuals that provide services to Oddup that facilitate the operation of the Oddup Services and community: for example, IT systems. You also understand and consent that the collection, processing, and use of your personal information by using Oddup Services may result in the cross-border transfer of that personal information. Your personal information may be shared or transferred as part of a change of control or sale of Oddup or to facilitate a restructuring or other corporate rearrangement. 

##### **YOU AND THE PUBLIC**

####  Certain personal information that you provide as part of your Oddup account will be made public or may be made public by you. We may also share information that you have made public on our site or third-party sites or services. 

##### **THIRD-PARTY SERVICES, ACCOUNTS AND PLATFORMS**

####  You may use your Oddup account with certain third-party services, accounts, and platforms as part of the Oddup Services or use third-party services, accounts, and platforms to access Oddup. If you select to do so then we may provide or share your account details and by doing so, you are providing us with consent. These third-party services, accounts, and platforms should have their own Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. You should review these before using third-party services, accounts, and platforms. We are not responsible for their collection, processing, or use of your personal information. 

##### **LAW**

####  You understand and consent that Oddup may be required to disclose your personal information when compelled by law, subpoena, court order, or other legal process. Oddup may also at its discretion process, use, and disclose your personal information where the protection of the public interest is involved. 

### **V. WHAT ARE YOUR RIGHTS?**

##### **YOUR INFORMATION**

####  You have the right to access, review, correct, or delete personal information and/or content in your Oddup account. You also have the right to close your account. You may have other statutory rights depending upon your jurisdiction with respect to the personal information that Oddup has collected in providing services to you. You are free at any time to contact us to exercise those statutory rights. 

##### **DATA RETENTION**

####  We will retain your personal information to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations. We reserve the right to retain personal information for a longer period if we have reasonable grounds for doing so including but not limited to a request from law enforcement, the resolution of a complaint, or the protection of our interests under this Privacy Policy or the User Agreement. We also retain the right to anonymize personal information and to retain that non-personal information at our discretion. 

##### **CONTACTING US**

####  You may contact us with respect to this Privacy Policy or your rights (statutory or otherwise) at  **rate@oddup.com** or by writing to us at: 

#### **Oddup Limited  
Privacy Officer  
1102, Hing Tai Commercial Building  
114 Wing Lok Street  
Sheung Wan, Hong Kong  
**

### **V. WHAT ELSE SHOULD YOU KNOW?**

##### **SECURITY**

####  We have adopted and follow generally accepted industry security safeguards and practices to protect your personal information. We cannot guarantee though the security of any information you transmit over the internet or provide to us or that we can eliminate risks associated with storing that information with your account - the internet is not a 100% secure ecosystem. We also cannot warrant that personal information cannot be accessed, used, or destroyed by third-parties despite the safeguards that we have implemented. You should also take appropriate measures to avoid disclosing publicly or through private messaging any information that may be of a personal nature. 

##### **CHILDREN**

####  We do not intend for Oddup to be used by those under the age of thirteen nor do we seek to collect information from those under that age. If we become aware that we have unitentionally collected any children's personal information without parental consent, we will delete it from our systems and close the account. 

##### **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

####  We reserve at our sole discretion the right to change this Privacy Policy from time-to-time. We will provide appropriate notice to you of any material changes to this Privacy Policy or any material changes in the way that we collect, process, or use your personal information. If you continue to use Oddup Services after notice of a material change, you will be considered to have consented to the change. If you do not wish to consent then you may close your account.
